[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
You should be close to the truth.
Isn't there anything you've realized?
Some secret they wouldn't mind killing a man to keep.
Have you caught on to something?
Kayoko Senba is a developmental biologist.
And what of it?
[Giving birth to you, was my greatest gift.] [Kaede]
You okay?
Hey, wait! Please!
Look.
You're searching for your nonexistent sister.
She exists.
Well, she doesn't exist on paper.
I can help you find her.
But I'll need you to work with me here.
We'll trade information.
I'll tell you what I know.
So talk to me, alright?
[The hidden truth of 27 years ago] [The identity of his sister]
Mother, your smoothie.
Have a good one.
I am Ishimizaki's daughter, Mari.
I came to ask about Shiharu Nanase.
Thank you, Mari.
Thank you.
I only wish we could have spoken sooner.
No, I...
Please, sit.
Thank you.
I owe you answers. Ask away.
What about this man here?
Can't say for sure. He's far away.
- I see. - Damn it!
Tada...
How the hell has he evaded every security camera in sight?
Are you sure you even saw this Ushio guy?
Tada.
I'll go search our files again.
Dr. Senba.
May I begin?
First, what inspired you to study genetics?
Ah, the usual.
Yes. I'm sure the question is a familiar one.
That, it is.
Usually, I tell people a book in my father's study inspired me.
And while that's no lie,
I had grown interested in the topic long before I knew of the study.
As a child, I often spent my summers
exploring my grandfather's garden
during our family visits to his place.
There, I happened to witness a mutant flower.
Upon noticing it, I felt an excitement unlike any I'd experienced before.
For that flower was a mistake made by God.
I realized then that even God made errors,
and felt a sort of sympathy for him.
And this inspired your genetic work?
It became my raison d'etre.
I wished to understand God. To stand beside him, as an equal.
It was the start to my twisted interest in life.
[Senba]
Come on.
Let's go.
Ready? Hold my hand.
Okay.
- What's for dinner? - Hamburgers?
- I wanna eat potatoes! - That sounds good, too.
Hirama. I'm doing it today.
You sure you can handle this alone?
Yes.
I can't cause you any more trouble.
I want to know where Shiharu is. [log.6]
Of course you do.
Shiharu couldn't do much on her own.
I don't think she could outrun an aggressive assailant.
Was Shiharu kidnapped by the person who murdered my father?
I hear you took great care of Shiharu.
Well...
I wouldn't say I took care of her.
I was just looking after a friend.
Thank you.
If anything, I'm grateful to her.
I'm truly blessed to have known Shii.
Sit.
Mari, can you bring us a towel?
You're freezing. Want to take a shower?
Right. That's a good idea.
Who is that girl?
She's the daughter of a relative.
Did we know anyone with a kid her age?
Yes, well...
The poor girl just lost both her parents.
So I've decided to take her in.
She's a sickly girl, who likely won't recover.
Mari, could you help me look after her?
You want me to take care of her?
But I'm no medical expert.
I'll help you along the way.
That's not the issue here.
This is partially for your sake, Mari.
I think you two will become fast friends.
What?
But...
Besides, you're not busy with work anyway.
I mean, I'm not, but...
You'll dry your hair, right?
Follow me.
Hm?
Nothing.
My father told me she couldn't leave the house much because she was sick.
But on days she was well, we went on walks at night.
It seems you two got along well.
We'd always talk about the silliest things.
They were precious moments to me.
I understand entirely.
Why did you leave your daughter with us?
I'm willing to accept whatever truth you have for me.
Just please, give me an answer.
Is my father part of the reason?
Yes.
The reason I entrusted my daughter to your family...
Is because Ishimizaki is also Shiharu's father.
Kyoichi Nanase and Akihiko Ishimizaki were college buds.
Which is how Haruka Nanase was let into Ishimizaki's lab.
Your point being?
The one who reported Haruka Nanase for trespassing, was Kayoko Senba.
Right.
Turns out, something does tie these four together.
Yes?
Mother, it's Keita!
Keita, he's...
What?
What about Keita?
Keita's been kidnapped!
What?
This is all my fault.
I was right there, and he just disappeared!
A man called while I was searching,
and threatened me not to tell the police...
Talk to me.
Is Keita safe?
The man said he would be, so long as I accept his demands.
He wants all your research on Roopkund.
- Hey there. - Hello.
Shinbashi, speaking.
Kayoko Senba is acting strange.
Can you look into it?
Yes, ma'am.
[Ishimizaki Family Grave]
Sir, your guest has arrived.
What did you mean by that earlier?
Sit, I'll explain everything.
Alright.
Is Shiharu really my father's daughter?
How about something to drink first?
Shiharu...
She is a child between myself, Ishimizaki,
and Kayoko Senba.
Kyoichi Nanase, Akihiko Ishimizaki, and Kayoko Senba
were all researching human remains at Roopkund 27 years ago.
It's a success!
Something's up between those three.
I reckon Haruka Nanase is also looking into it.
These are the ledgers from companies who assisted with "log.0".
- Thank you. - Was there anything left?
No. I made sure any trace of money no longer leads back to us.
If there is any more evidence on "log.0", I'll make sure to erase it myself.
Show yourself.
I know it's you.
Where is Keita? Give him back.
First, I have questions to ask you.
Keita is not here, but he is safe.
Can you promise me that?
Yes.
You, my father, and Professor Ishimizaki.
I want to know what research you three were doing for Nichie and Plantae,
and how it all ties back to Shiharu.
"Shiharu"?
My younger sister.
Professor Ishimizaki sent you an email.
He said he was prepared to atone.
The Plantae revere Roopkund, and call it the Land of Souls.
The very same Roopkund you three were researching.
And...
There is something my sister once said.
This really is a beautiful place.
In May, the local elementary schoolers come to do plant cuttings here.
- Plant cutting? - Yeah.
They replant the stem of a hydrangea, and it grows into a new one.
Did the stairs tire you?
These hydrangeas...
They're the same as me.
Shiharu...
was a plant cutting.
Herbert John Webber, a plant physiologist,
used another, more commonly known term
to refer to plant cuttings.
He called them, "clones".
The research you three immersed yourselves in,
was the revival of the dead.
Shiharu Nanase, who grew up as Kyoichi Nanase's daughter,
is an asexually reproduced clone, isn't she?
That clone...
It was successfully born?
You all are former believers of Plantae, correct?
Then as I briefly alluded to earlier,
please tell us what occurred in Plantae, 27 years ago.
This man here will pay you for your time today.
Your reward will depend on how much you tell us.
You didn't know about Shiharu?
I was kept in the complete dark.
How involved in all this are you?
I said, I know nothing.
Can you even create a clone from bones as old as those in Roopkund?
If, theoretically speaking, you were to create a human clone,
you'd have to take the nucleus from a cell, and inject it into an egg cell.
Then transplant that cell into a host to give birth.
But...
But that's only theoretically speaking.
We've barely succeeded cloning mice, but humans? That's...
Possible.
The greatest challenge was using the deteriorating nuclei from a dead body.
How did you resolve that issue?
I developed a method of repairing the nucleus,
by repeatedly transplanting nuclei into egg cells, and initiating repairs there.
What? A complete repair would be impossible.
Each egg cell would only repair a section.
I'd then take that partially repaired nucleus,
and transplant it into another egg cell for further repairs.
Repeat that over and over,
in a set amount of time, and voilà.
But some damage still remained.
Without my knowledge, we wouldn't even have results.
If I weren't on the team, there wouldn't be a baby.
What happened to the clone?
You refuse to tell me.
Who ordered you to do this?
My father? Plantae?
It all began when my gene therapy research
was cut short by religious groups in the UK.
I had returned to Japan, hoping for more.
Yes?
You must be Dr. Kayoko Senba.
And you are?
I would like your help in reviving our Holy One.
Who is this "Holy One" you're referring to?
Sojiro Manabe. The founder of Plantae.
Plantae?
What does a religious group like yours want from a scientist like myself?
Before Brother Sojiro Manabe passed away,
he claimed men would not inherit the Plantae.
Rather, it would be a Holy Woman revived from the Land of Souls
who would unite all life on Earth.
He wanted me to unearth the remains of a woman from Roopkund,
and replicate her.
You want me to create a clone from an ancient skeleton?
Yes.
I want you to create us a Holy Woman.
You're asking the impossible.
You can't create a person from dead cells.
I'm relieved.
A normal scientist would first decline by bringing up ethics.
If the issue is the necessary skill and technology, Plantae will assist,
as well as Nichie Pharmaceutical's Yumihiko Nanase.
Even so...
God tested Brother Manabe, and left him unable to produce a child.
This is our only way.
You ought to have created a clone while he was still alive.
We did.
However, Brother Manabe was irreplaceable.
No one could accept I was his successor.
How about it, Dr. Senba?
"This man sitting in front of me is a clone?"
At first, I couldn't believe him.
But if he were telling the truth...
I could overcome any sort of boundary,
and pursue my research with as many resources as I wished.
That is an opportunity every researcher dreams of.
Won't you join us, in creating a God?
No.
For I would become God.
So you created a human being.
It was ironic.
Overseas, religious views on ethics hindered scientific breakthroughs.
While in Japan, religion overcame such ethical boundaries with ease.
You people had to find a host who would give birth to the clone.
How did you choose the mother?
Did Plantae offer some of their people?
Indeed.
They gathered young women?
Yes.
They said Brother Manabe needed our assistance,
so female worshippers in their twenties signed up for a health checkup.
Was an employee from Nichie in charge of these checkups?
We do not know who the doctor was.
But an individual from Nichie was overseeing the whole process.
30 women signed up for the exam.
They wanted a woman who would carry Brother Manabe's child!
I thought Brother Manabe had passed away by this time.
I believe he had his sperm frozen.
The girl who was chosen was overjoyed.
She was so grateful to be of use.
It was like watching a sacrifice be blind with happiness.
The way they treated women as mere birth-giving vessels
had me become disillusioned with Plantae as a whole.
What did you tell those chosen five?
Did you tell them about the clone?
Of course not.
Just that we needed their assistance in creating a Holy Woman.
At least, that's how the Plantae organizer explained it.
And who was this organizer?
The current Head of PR,
Kasuga. She practically runs the organization at this point.
As a result of our experiment, one woman successfully took the cell.
My mother.
Kaede Tozaki.
She was my mother.
I can't believe this.
You're saying Shiharu was an artificially-made human being?
Was this all your doing?
The project began with my father.
Back then, I was desperate for his approval.
I clearly couldn't see my surroundings.
I even got Ishimizaki involved.
Why?
Why would you rope my father into this?
Isn't that why he died?
Why he was murdered?
I don't know.
But I deeply regret getting him involved.
He was the only person I trusted.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
And are you okay?
Yes.
Where is Shii?
Where is Shiharu?
She's safe, right?
Please, tell me the truth.
I want to see her again!
Shiharu is...
Shiharu is dead.
My mother died.
I see.
That's it?
You're thinking she died because she gave birth to a clone?
Can you prove me wrong?
One of Plantae's executives.
Why is she here?
The girl next to her is my junior.
Then she's a fellow devotee.
Everyone's connected somehow.
Sir?
What are you doing? Follow your orders.
I'm compiling my findings for you, Chief.
Ishimizaki, Kyoichi Nanase, and Senba Kayoko were at Roopkund...
Digging into that isn't your job.
But...
Just do the work you've been given.
That's how an organization keeps functioning.
What did he need?
The higher-ups want me to stop.
I'm not surprised,
since you aren't following orders.
Something's up with Roopkund.
Ishimizaki blamed himself.
So he felt guilty about my mother.
After the passing of the previous head of Nichie,
your step-grandfather, Yumihiko Nanase,
the clone project
was entirely called off.
If that's enough, then return Keita to me.
Professor Ishimizaki wanted to go public with the truth, didn't he?
I was entirely against it.
Is that why you killed him?
I did no such thing.
Then was it my father?
I received Ishimizaki's email about atoning
several days before he was killed.
I thought he planned to make our findings public.
How did you reply to him?
I had planned to see him that day.
I wanted to talk, before he did anything rash.
Ishimizaki?
You...
I think he was killed because he tried to reveal our secret.
That should be enough.
Where is Keita?
Hand me your findings first.
This is what killed Ishimizaki.
If you make it public, I will be...
You won't be safe, either.
I won't be making it public.
Keita is already with Tomoe.
Wow!
- Again! - Again?
You speedster.
Great job!
I see.
You got Tomoe on your side.
That woman...
You have no right to condemn Tomoe.
You killed my mother.
Your mother understood the risks.
Nothing was guaranteed.
We even gave her a thorough explanation.
You people took advantage of her faith.
You knew worshippers would do anything for the organization.
If she was faithful, so be it.
Quit avoiding the main issue here.
I see.
I thought you would be more understanding.
What a shame.
Oh, I understand.
You're frustrated that your accomplishments aren't seeing the light of day.
You could never understand the possibilities I was denied.
Playing the victim, huh?
Do you even feel guilt?
What more could I have done?
So you'll instead forget the humans you've used.
You could never understand.
I hope I never do. Because I wish to remain human.
And you. You're no god.
I was told
your sister was a stillbirth.
Your father and Ishimizaki hid her existence from me.
Why do you think that is?
Before venting at me, you ought to check your surroundings first.
- Please come again. - Thank you.
Thank you.
I'll have my chauffeur drive us home.
I'd like to think on this alone.
Then I'll call a taxi for you.
I'd prefer walking home.
Even I don't know what exactly is going on.
Please refrain from doing anything dangerous.
Okay.
And you won't look into anything unnecessary?
I won't.
Good. Take care.
Thank you.
- Shii. - Hm?
Is there anything you want to do when you're older?
I don't know. I don't even live a normal life.
What about you?
Me?
I don't have any lofty dreams.
- You don't? - Nope.
But I guess I'd want to be hired at a sizable company.
Somewhere that'd let me get off work on time.
A place that's only an hour train ride away from Dad's place.
And when I visit my usual store on my way home from work,
I'd know all the regulars there.
- Sounds like a nice future. - Right?
The store has a delicious menu,
and all the regulars taste test new dishes,
and give the chef our honest reviews.
It's like you're talking from experience.
The store down there was especially good.
And now you are?
Yup. Since I never had a mom,
I used to meet Dad there for dinner.
We ate there practically every single day.
Sounds nice.
So even as a kid, I'd say my favorite food was minced fish.
None of the other kids could relate.
This is the store.
It closed down?
Yeah. Competition built up and all that.
- I see. - Yeah.
I've got it. My dream.
What is it?
We'll run a store together.
One that serves delicious minced fish.
Sounds fun.
You okay? Are you tired?
I'm fine.
I want to walk a bit longer.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Sir. Isn't there something you've been hiding from me?
This is Nanase, speaking.
Yes. I've finished speaking with her.
Yes.
She realized I was helping you, didn't she?
I would've loved to see her face.
It's fine. I won't be returning home anyway.
The next time I'll see her will either be the divorce, or in court.
I'll be living in a hotel for a while.
Thank you, really.
No, thank you.
Take care.
Is that good?
- Yeah! - Then is that your dinner?
- No! - Thought so.
Hello.
I thought I told you to stay out of this.
I have something to tell you about the human you created.
The girl from Roopkund is alive.